smarterfox.com 2014-04-22

# Privacy Policy - FastestFox: Browse Faster

Your privacy is important to us. Below is our privacy policy. (Note, this privacy policy is available under a Creative Commons Sharealike license. It is based on [Automattic](http://automattic.com/)'s privacy policy.) If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team. AddonReactor, LLC. (“AddonReactor”) operates several websites and browser extensions, including smarterfox.com, FastestFox, and FastestFox for Chrome. It is AddonReactor's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, AddonReactor collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. AddonReactor’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how AddonReactor’s visitors use its website. From time to time, AddonReactor may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. AddonReactor also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on WordPress.com blogs. AddonReactor only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to AddonReactor’s websites choose to interact with AddonReactor in ways that require AddonReactor to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that AddonReactor gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at our website to provide a username and email address. In each case, AddonReactor collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with AddonReactor. AddonReactor does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

AddonReactor may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites or the users of its software. For instance, AddonReactor may monitor the most frequently used feature. AddonReactor may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, AddonReactor does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

AddonReactor discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on AddonReactor’s behalf or to provide services available at AddonReactor’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using AddonReactor’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. AddonReactor will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, AddonReactor discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when AddonReactor believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of AddonReactor, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an AddonReactor website and have supplied your email address, AddonReactor may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with AddonReactor and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. AddonReactor takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. AddonReactor uses cookies to help AddonReactor identify and track visitors, their usage of AddonReactor website, and their website access preferences. AddonReactor visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using AddonReactor’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of AddonReactor’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If AddonReactor, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that AddonReactor goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of AddonReactor may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by AddonReactor and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, AddonReactor may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in AddonReactor’s sole discretion. AddonReactor encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
